{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"ECHO Volunteer, Donna Johnson","title":"ECHO Welcome Center: Assisting Our Community One Neighbor at a Time","description":"Volunteer Training","email":"","website":"https://echofl.org/","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":12858,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":24,"width":1174,"height":777,"responsive":true,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5366","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Title","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":363},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5366"}}},{"id":"Slide5388","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Module Introduction","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1002},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5388"}}},{"id":"Slide5404","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Objective","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1062},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5404"}}},{"id":"Slide5420","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"ECHO Overview – Mission","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":834},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5420"}}},{"id":"Slide6368","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"ECHO Overview – Locations","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":333},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6368"}}},{"id":"si5466","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5480","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5488","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5492","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5488_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5499","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5503","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5499_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5436q0","for":"Slide5436q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5550","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5436q0","for":"Slide5436q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5563","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5436q0","for":"Slide5436q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5520","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5436q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5507","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5436q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5436","class":"Question Slide","instance":"KC1","thumbnail":"","children":["si5466","si5473","si5492","si5503","si5533","si5550","si5563","si5520","si5507"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5436"},"question":{"interactionId":"5453","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Slide6384","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Active Listening – Introduction","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":684},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6384"}}},{"id":"Slide6400","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Active Listening - Purpose","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1044},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6400"}}},{"id":"Slide6416","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Active Listening – Skills","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":630},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6416"}}},{"id":"Slide7364","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Active Listening – Skills 2","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":558},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7364"}}},{"id":"si6462","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6469","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6476","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6484","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6488","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6484_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6495","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6499","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6495_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6432q1","for":"Slide6432q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6546","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6432q1","for":"Slide6432q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6432q1","for":"Slide6432q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6516","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6432q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6503","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6432q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6432","class":"Question Slide","instance":"KC2","thumbnail":"","children":["si6462","si6469","si6488","si6499","si6529","si6546","si6559","si6516","si6503"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6432"},"question":{"interactionId":"6449","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Slide7472","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures - Introduction","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7472"}}},{"id":"Slide7488","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures – Data Gathering","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":597},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7488"}}},{"id":"Slide7519","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures – Proof of Residence","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":288},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7519"}}},{"id":"Slide7535","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures – Proof of Identification","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":369},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7535"}}},{"id":"Slide7551","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures – Social Security Information","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":504},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7551"}}},{"id":"Slide7567","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures – Contingency ","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":624},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7567"}}},{"id":"Slide7583","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures – Referrals","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":981},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7583"}}},{"id":"Slide7599","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Intake Procedures – Unity Forms","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":960},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7599"}}},{"id":"Slide7600","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Assistance & Resources","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1011},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7600"}}},{"id":"Slide7631","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Assistance & Resources","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":474},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7631"}}},{"id":"si6601","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6608","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6615","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6623","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6627","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6623_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6638","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6634_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6571q2","for":"Slide6571q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6685","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6571q2","for":"Slide6571q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6698","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6571q2","for":"Slide6571q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6655","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6571q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6642","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6571q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6571","class":"Question Slide","instance":"KC3","thumbnail":"","children":["si6601","si6608","si6627","si6638","si6668","si6685","si6698","si6655","si6642"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6571"},"question":{"interactionId":"6588","quizId":379,"title":"True/False","text":"Type the question here","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Slide7647","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Conclusion","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7647"}}},{"id":"si5605","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5612","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5619","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5627","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5631","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5638","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5642","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5672","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5575q3","for":"Slide5575q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5689","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5575q3","for":"Slide5575q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5702","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5575q3","for":"Slide5575q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5659","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5575q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5575q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5575","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5605","si5612","si5631","si5642","si5672","si5689","si5702","si5659","si5646"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5575"},"question":{"interactionId":"5592","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"ECHO Welcome Center","class":"project","title":"ECHO Welcome Center","children":["Slide5366","Slide5388","Slide5404","Slide5420","Slide6368","Slide5436","Slide6384","Slide6400","Slide6416","Slide7364","Slide6432","Slide7472","Slide7488","Slide7519","Slide7535","Slide7551","Slide7567","Slide7583","Slide7599","Slide7600","Slide7631","Slide6571","Slide7647","Slide5575"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide5436q0","Slide6432q1","Slide6571q2","Slide5575q3"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"navigationEnabled":true,"navigateVisitedSlides":false,"collapseAll":false,"showTopicDuration":true,"statusFlag":true,"selfPaced":false,"showSearch":true,"enabled":true},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":true,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5366","title":"Title","visible":true},{"id":"Slide5388","title":"Module Introduction","visible":true},{"id":"Slide5404","title":"Objective","visible":true},{"id":"Slide5420","title":"ECHO Overview – Mission","visible":true},{"id":"Slide6368","title":"ECHO Overview – Locations","visible":true},{"id":"Slide5436","title":"KC1","visible":true},{"id":"Slide6384","title":"Active Listening – Introduction","visible":true},{"id":"Slide6400","title":"Active Listening - Purpose","visible":true},{"id":"Slide6416","title":"Active Listening – Skills","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7364","title":"Active Listening – Skills 2","visible":true},{"id":"Slide6432","title":"KC2","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7472","title":"Intake Procedures - Introduction","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7488","title":"Intake Procedures – Data Gathering","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7519","title":"Intake Procedures – Proof of Residence","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7535","title":"Intake Procedures – Proof of Identification","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7551","title":"Intake Procedures – Social Security Information","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7567","title":"Intake Procedures – Contingency ","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7583","title":"Intake Procedures – Referrals","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7599","title":"Intake Procedures – Unity Forms","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7600","title":"Assistance & Resources","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7631","title":"Assistance & Resources","visible":true},{"id":"Slide6571","title":"KC3","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7647","title":"Conclusion","visible":true},{"id":"Slide5575","title":"Slide 24","visible":true}]}